18 exclusive we learned from sources
that bharti enterprise may sell its
entire stake in ics lumbar general
insurance yash is here with the details
yes
rima this is a large transaction in the
general insurance space what sources
tell us is that bharti enterprises is
looking to sell its entire stake in
icici lombard general insurance uh this
particular transaction of sale of stake
from bharti enterprises could happen
through a block deal and uh sources tell
us that the target is uh the early part
of next week itself so of course not too
far as far as the transaction timeline
is concerned uh as far as the stake
itself is concerned bharti enterprises
owns about 3.72 stake in icsa lombard
general insurance and at the current
market price uh the transaction uh could
be worth 2200 crore rupees uh do
remember that when bharti axa uh was uh
you know the merger between bharti acts
and icsl lombard was announced both
owners of bharti aksa that is bharti
enterprises and axa got nearly four
percent stake in icici lombard axa
exited its part of stake that was in
last year and now bharti enterprises is
looking to sell its part when it comes
to ici lombard general insurance we've
written to both parties involved in this
particular transaction bharti
enterprises has replied saying that they
do not comment on market speculation we
are still awaiting a response from icsa
alabama got it all right yash thanks a
lot for that well let's get in the pin